[♪♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig. Snort.
This is
my little brother George.
Oink, oink.
This is Mummy Pig.
[SNORTS]
And this is Daddy Pig.
Peppa Pig. Snort.
[♪♪♪]
PEPPA:
"The Tree House."
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are visiting
Granny Pig and Grandpa Pig.
[KNOCKS]
Granny Pig.
Ganggy Ig.
Hello, my little ones.
Snort.
Before you come
in the house,
you must take off
your muddy boots.
Yes, Granny.
Oink.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Peppa, George,
look what I've made.
Little curtains.
Ooh.
What are the little curtains
for, Granny?
It's a surprise. Snort.
Do you want to see what
Grandpa Pig has made for you
in the garden?
Yes, please.
Oink, oink.
[GIGGLING]
Grandpa Pig.
Baba Ig.
Hello, Peppa, George.
Look what I've made
for you.
Snort. A tree house.
A tree house
for George and me?
Hee-hee-hee.
Oink, oink.
And the little curtains are
for your tree house.
Hooray!
Peppa and George
love their tree house.
Thank you, Granny Pig.
Thank you, Grandpa Pig.
Oink, oink.
Ho-ho. Snort. Who wants
to go inside first?
Me! Me!
In you go, then.
Before I go in my tree house,
I must take off my muddy boots.
I'm in my tree house.
[SING-SONG]
[GIGGLES]
Oink, oink.
George,
would you like
to go
in the tree house too?
Oink, oink.
Yes? Who is it?
A young pig named George
would like to pay a visit.
Snort. Can he come in?
As long as he takes off
his muddy boots.
George,
take your boots off,
then you can visit Peppa
in the tree house.
[GIGGLES]
[SING-SONG]
Who is it?
Oink.
George?
Oink, oink.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Yes?
[SING-SONG] Who is it?
Snort.
It's Mummy Pig.
Have you room
for any more visitors?
Hm. You have to say
the secret words.
Then you can come
into our house.
[GIGGLES]
I see. And what are
the secret words?
I have to whisper them
to you.
The secret words are
"Daddy's Big Tummy."
I see. Ha-ha.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Say the secret words.
Daddy's Big Tummy.
That's right.
Snort. I think those
are silly secret words.
[LAUGHING]
Mummy, before you come
in our house,
you must take off
your boots.
Of course.
[GIGGLING]
Snort. There's room
for Daddy too.
Say the secret words,
Daddy.
Can I have different
secret words, please?
ALL: No.
Oh, all right.
Daddy's Big Tummy.
[LAUGH]
That's right.
You can come in now, Daddy.
Snort. Take your boots off.
[GRUNTS]
Uh, I don't think I can fit
through the door.
[GIGGLES]
That's because your tummy's
too big.
[LAUGH]
Snort. I know.
Daddy Pig can climb in
through the top.
Peppa, George,
Mummy Pig and Daddy Pig
are all in the tree house.
[ALL LAUGH]
Granny, I love our tree house.
I don't want to ever come out.
That's nice, Peppa.
But are you sure you don't want
to visit me in my house?
No, thank you, Granny.
In that case,
Grandpa Pig and I
will just have to eat
my homemade cookies
all by ourselves.
Snort. Cookies!
[GIGGLES]
Granny Pig.
Here are
my homemade cookies.
But if you want to come in,
you have to say
the secret words.
That's easy.
Daddy's Big Tummy.
That's right.
[ALL LAUGH]
Well, I still think that those
are very silly secret words.
[ALL LAUGHING, SNORTING]
PEPPA:
"Fancy Dress Party."
Peppa and George are having
a fancy dress party.
All their friends
are invited.
Peppa is dressed
as a fairy princess.
Snort.
And George is dressed
as a dinosaur.
Grr! Dine-saur.
Hee-hee-hee.
[HORN BEEPS]
Here are Peppa's friends--
Candy Cat, Suzy Sheep,
Danny Dog,
Rebecca Rabbit
and Pedro Pony.
Baa.
Suzy is wearing
her nurse's costume.
[DING-DONG]
Snort.
Hello, Suzy.
Baa.
Hello, Mr. Pig.
I'm glad the nurse has arrived.
Have you just come
from the hospital?
Uh, I'm not a real nurse.
It's just pretend.
Ho-ho-ho. Very good.
My, my.
Who have we here?
Woof, woof.
I'm a pirate.
Shiver me timbers.
Ha-ha-ha.
Meow. I'm a witch.
I can turn you into a frog.
[NICKERS, NEIGHS]
I'm a clown.
[BEEPS]
Ha-ha-ha.
That's funny.
Snort. And what are you,
Rebecca Rabbit?
I'm a carrot.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Fantastic. Come in.
There's a fairy princess
and a dinosaur waiting
to meet you.
[ALL GIGGLE]
Snort. Hello, everyone.
ALL:
Hello, Peppa.
Hello, Suzy.
I'm Princess Peppa. Snort.
You must bow
when you speak to me.
Hello, Your Majesty. Baa.
I'm Nurse Suzy.
Open wide and say ahh.
Ahh.
[GIGGLE]
Neigh. I'm a clown.
Do something funny.
[BEEP]
[GIGGLES]
Woof. Rebecca, why are you
dressed as a carrot?
I like carrots.
[ALL LAUGH]
Grrr. Dine-saur.
[GASPS]
A scary dinosaur.
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa is admiring herself
in the mirror.
Mirror, mirror on the wall,
who's the fairest of them all?
Snort.
[GHOSTLY VOICE]
You are, Peppa.
[GIGGLES]
Meow. Hello, Peppa.
[NORMAL VOICE]
Hello. I'm a little
fairy princess. Snort.
I'm a witch. Meow.
And I've got a magic wand.
I've got a magic wand too.
I can turn you into a frog.
And I'll turn you
into a frog.
Aah!
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Dine-saur. Grrr!
[GASPS]
[CRYING]
Oh, dear, George is scared
of his own reflection.
Oh, silly George.
Look, it's you
in the mirror.
Hee-hee-hee. Grr.
Children,
it's time to decide
who has the best
fancy dress costume.
Snort.
We need a judge.
Me.
Ho-ho-ho.
As it's Peppa's party,
maybe she should be
the judge.
Snort.
[SING-SONG]
I'm the judge.
Daddy, what is a judge?
The judge decides
who has the best costume.
Snort. Oh, goody.
Peppa is going to choose
who has the best costume.
Suzy, can I see
your costume, please?
Baa. I'm Nurse Suzy.
I make people better.
Very good, Nurse Suzy.
Snort. Now Danny.
Woof. I'm a pirate.
Shiver me timbers.
Hee-hee-hee. Now Candy.
Meow. I'm a witch.
I can turn you
into a frog.
Well, I'm a fairy princess,
and I can turn you into a frog.
[SNORTS]
Phbbt.
Children,
children.
Sorry, Mummy.
Who's next?
[HORN BEEPS]
I'm a clown.
[BEEPS]
Hee-hee-hee. That's funny.
Snort. And Rebecca.
I'm a carrot. Ha-ha-ha.
Lovely.
Oink.
[GIGGLES]
And my little brother George
is a scary dinosaur.
Grrr.
Everyone's costume
is very good.
ALL:
Hooray!
Now you say
who the winner is.
Oh, yes. Ahem.
And the winner is...
Me.
[BOTH GASP]
[ALL GASP]
Peppa, you can't pick yourself.
You're the judge.
Oh. Can't I?
You have to pick
another winner.
Okay. The carrot wins.
CHILDREN:
Hooray!
Thank you. Ha-ha-ha.
Peppa loves
fancy dress parties.
Everyone loves
[ALL LAUGH]
PEPPA:
"The Museum."
Peppa and her family are going
to the museum.
[GEORGE AND PEPPA GIGGLE]
Snort. Daddy,
what is a museum?
Snort.
It's a place full
of interesting things
that are very old.
Older than you?
Yes, even older than me.
Ooh.
Ooooh.
Really old.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Snort. There's one room
full of things
that belonged to kings
and queens from long ago.
I want to see
the king and queen's room.
And there's another room
with a real dinosaur.
Wow. Dine-saur. Grrr!
[ALL LAUGH]
Hello, Mummy Pig.
Snort.
Hello, Miss Rabbit.
How many tickets,
please?
Two adults
and two children.
Dine-saur. Grrr!
Ha-ha.
And a dinosaur.
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa wants to see
the room full of things
that belong to kings and queens
from long ago.
Wow.
Oink. Dine-saur?
But George wants
to see the real dinosaur.
[FUSSES]
Snort.
Don't worry, George.
We will see
the dinosaur next.
Oink, oink.
Peppa,
these are all the things
that the queen had
a long time ago.
This is the queen's
special chair.
It's called a throne.
Snort. It's beautiful.
This is the queen's dress.
Snort. It's so pretty.
Look, Peppa. This is
the queen's golden crown.
Wow! Snort.
What lovely things.
Mummy, where is
the queen's television?
They didn't have
television then.
Aah. No television?
Snort.
But they did have computers?
No, they didn't have
computers either.
Snort.
What did they do all day?
[BOTH LAUGH]
Snort.
Mummy, if I was the queen,
I would eat as much cake
as I wanted.
Peppa imagines being a queen.
[TRUMPET FANFARE PLAYING]
[GIGGLES]
[GOBBLES]
Mmm, delicious.
Is there anything else
you would care for,
Queen Peppa?
Yes.
More cake, please.
Of course.
[GIGGLES, SNORTS]
DADDY PIG [ECHOING]:
Come on, everyone.
Coming, Daddy.
[GIGGLES]
Daddy, I'm Queen Peppa.
You must bow
when you speak to me.
Oh, I'm most terribly sorry,
Your Royal Highness.
And what do you do?
I'm your daddy.
Hm, that must be
very interesting.
Yes, it's very interesting.
And what room is this?
This is the dinosaur room.
Snort! The dinosaur room?
George, this is
the dinosaur room.
Hee-hee-hee. Dine-saur.
Where is the dinosaur?
He's somewhere in the room.
I can't see him.
He must be very small.
Oink.
DADDY PIG:
Actually, Peppa,
he's very big.
[GASPS]
Wow.
These are the bones
of a real dinosaur.
Hee-hee-hee.
Oink. Dine-saur.
[ECHOES] Grr!
[GEORGE AND PEPPA GIGGLE]
George imagines
being a big dinosaur.
Snort. Rrawrr!
Aah!
Rrawrr-awrr!
It's a dinosaur!
Help! Help!
Rrawrr-awrr!
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Ha-ha. The dinosaur room
is George's favorite room.
Oink. Hee-hee-hee.
My favorite room is
the king and queen's room.
And it looks as if Daddy Pig
is already
in his favorite room.
Which room is that,
Mummy?
The room
with the cakes in.
Daddy Pig's favorite room
is the museum café.
[LAUGH]
Snort.
Come on, tuck in.
Oh, yes. Snort.
This is
a very nice room.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
PEPPA:
"Very Hot Day."
The sun is shining.
It is a very hot day.
Snort.
What a lovely hot day.
[GIGGLING]
Peppa and George
are wearing their boots.
They are going to jump
in muddy puddles.
I love muddy puddles.
Oh.
Oh, dear.
The sun is so hot
that the puddles have dried up.
Mummy, Daddy,
the puddles are all dry
and we can't jump
in them.
Never mind, Peppa.
It's so sunny, you can play
in the paddling pool instead.
Yes, the paddling pool!
Oink, oink.
MUMMY PIG:
First you have to change
into your swimming costumes.
Yes, Mummy.
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa and George are wearing
their swimming costumes.
Mummy Pig is wearing
her swimming costume
and Daddy Pig is wearing
his swimming costume.
Snort. Because it's so hot,
you need sun cream.
Yuck!
It's all oily and yucky.
Yuck.
Oh-ho-ho,
what a fuss about nothing.
Yes, we all need sun cream
today.
Oh. Hee-hee-hee-hee-hee.
Ho-ho. Snort.
Come on, George.
Oink, oink.
Hee-hee-hee.
Let's get some air
into this paddling pool.
Daddy Pig is pumping up
the paddling pool.
Oof.
Easy as pie.
[GIGGLES, SNORTS]
[GIGGLES]
Peppa holds the hose
and Mummy Pig
turns on the water.
[GURGLING]
Snort. Where's the water?
Whaaa!
[GIGGLES]
[GEORGE AND PEPPA GIGGLING]
Peppa and George
love their paddling pool.
[BICYCLE BELL RINGS]
WOMAN:
Ice cream! Ice cream!
Miss Rabbit,
the ice cream lady. Snort!
[RINGS BELL]
Ice cream!
On very hot days,
Miss Rabbit sells ice cream.
Mummy, Daddy?
Snort.
Can George and I
have an ice cream, please?
Oh, well, I suppose it is
an especially hot day.
Hooray!
Please,
can I have one as well?
Everyone likes ice cream.
Hello, Mummy Pig,
Peppa and George.
Hello, Miss Rabbit.
Snort.
What ice creams
would you like?
Can I have a cone, please,
Miss Rabbit?
Of course you may,
Peppa.
Thank you.
Snort.
The same for me.
And one for Daddy Pig,
please.
And what would
young Mr. George like?
Dine-saur.
A dinosaur?
Silly George.
He always says "dinosaur"
for everything.
Well, it just so happens
that I do have
a dinosaur-shaped ice-lolly.
[GIGGLES]
Dine-saur. Grrr!
George, you should eat
your ice-lolly
before it melts.
Dine-saur.
George loves
his dinosaur ice-lolly so much,
he doesn't want to eat it.
Thank you, Miss Rabbit.
Enjoy the weather.
[RINGS BELL]
[GIGGLE]
George, I really think
you should eat your ice-lolly
before it melts and...
falls on the ground.
Waaaah!
Oh, dear, George's dinosaur
ice-lolly has melted
and fallen on the ground.
Never mind, George.
You can share
Daddy's ice cream.
I'm sure he won't mind.
[GIGGLES]
[SNORING]
It is so warm,
Daddy Pig has fallen asleep.
Snort.
Daddy Pig does look hot.
Let's tip water on Daddy
to cool him down.
Good idea, Peppa.
Whoa! Snort.
What happened?
You were all red and hot,
Daddy Pig.
So we tipped water on you.
Oh, I see.
Thank you, Peppa.
[LAUGH]
Snort.
Look, the puddles are back!
Quick, George,
let's get our boots.
Oink, oink.
[GIGGLING]
Peppa and George
are wearing their boots.
[GIGGLING]
Peppa and George
love the hot day,
but most of all, they love
jumping up and down in puddles.
Oh, ho-ho-ho.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
[♪♪♪]
PEPPA:
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTS, GIGGLES]
GEORGE:
Oink, oink.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTS]